FRANCISCO ROMO

FRONT END DEVELOPER

22 Windlfower Way, Whitby 416-722-8742 mail@pacoromo.ca linkedin.com/in/francisco-j-romo

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Front end developer with experience building applications with React, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, and API Integration. Posseses strong conflict resolution skills to solve both personal and technical problems. Positive reputation for quality work and timely delivery. Past experience in the auto repair industry with strong troubleshooting capabilities.

SKILLS TECH STACK

Conflict resolutionQuality orientedJavaScriptReactAdaptationFluent in EnglishCSSSass

Strong critical thinking skills Fluent in Spanish (Native) HTML Restful API

Execution Organized Responsive Design Git

EDUCATION

Juno College of Technology, Toronto Ontario

Javascript & Immersive Web Development

Aug 2021 - Nov 2022

Universidad Autonoma de Aguascalientes, Mexico

Bachelor in Electronics and Digital Communication Engineering

WORK EXPERIENCE

Auto Electrico Especializado Romo

Consulting Engineer, Aguascalientes, Mexico

Aug, 2020 - Sep, 2022

- Established an online presence by developing a website and major social media platforms
- Managed to place the shop as the top rated bussiness in the industry statewide
- Implemented a sofware based workflow, resulting in a 30% drop in customer rescheduling

Auto Electrico Especializado Romo

Floor manager/Technician Consultant, Aguascalientes, Mexico

Dec, 2019 - Jul, 2020

- A complete change in customer experience by implementing online scheduling technologies
- Implemented PC based test systems reducing part refurbishing times by more than 20%

Auto Electrico Especializado Romo

Technician Consultant, Aguascalientes, Mexico

Apr, 2001 - Nov, 2019

- Developed quality control protocols reducing warranty inicidence rate by 30%
- Trained more than 30 Technicians currently active.